<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!DOCTYPE knimeNode PUBLIC "-//UNIKN//DTD KNIME Node 2.0//EN" "http://www.knime.org/Node.dtd">
<knimeNode icon="pmmlensemblepredictor.png" type="Predictor" deprecated="true">
    <name>PMML Ensemble Predictor</name>
    
    <shortDescription>
        Predicts data using a ensemble model
    </shortDescription>
    
    <fullDescription>
        <intro>
            The PMML Ensemble Predictor node takes a pmml document containing an ensemble of other models and executes all
            of them on the given data. The results from all models are then aggregated using a method specified in the ensemble
            model. The output contains a column for each prediction of the single models (if set in the settings)
            and one column with the combined result.
            Note that ensembles of ensembles are not supported with the exception of Gradient Boosted Trees which are treated base model.
            It's on the other hand not possible to predict Gradient Boosted Trees models with this predictor, please use the PMML Predictor node
            or the Gradient Boosted Trees Predictor (PMML) nodes for this task.
        </intro>
        <option name="Return individual predictions">Determines whether the output contains
        one column for each model's prediction</option>
        <option name="Multiple model method as column name">Determines whether the column with the combined
        predictions should be named after the combination method</option>
        <option name="Tie break">Determines what is output when there is a tie between two classes in the combination
        methods majority vote and weighted majority vote</option>
    </fullDescription>
    
    <ports>
        <inPort index="0" name="PMML Ensemble">A PMML Model containing an ensemble mining model</inPort>
        <inPort index="1" name="Input data">Data to be predicted</inPort>
        <outPort index="0" name="Prediction">Prediction of every single model and the aggregated ensemble prediction</outPort>
    </ports>    
</knimeNode>
